Finding Aid for the Ayres & Fiege Architectural Drawings LSC.0115
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 3: Commercial buildings., 1945-1969
  - ., 1948 (Folder 56)
    - Armstrong Market Building., 1948, 1950.; 6.; 16 items.
      Job Number 720, 822. Armstrong Market Building
      19205 Moorpark, North Hollywood, CA.
      Owner: E.W. Armstrong.
    - Bee Line Aero., 1948.; 7.; 5 items.
      Job Number 724. Bee Line Aero--sales room and garage
      Van Nuys, CA.
      Copy of engineer's calculations.
      Owner: Bee-Line Aero Sale Corp.
  - ., 1949 (Folder 57)
    - Steensen Restaurant Building., 1949.; 1.; 1 item.
      Job Number 749. Steensen Restaurant Building--addition
      20109 Saticoy St.
      Original drawings for lath House, store building and warehouse: plans, sections, elevations, details.
      Plot plan.
      Owner: Mr. C.I. Steensen.
    - Winchester Restaurant., 1949.; 2.; 1 item.
      See also Map folder 63, item 1.
      Job Number 756. Winchester Restaurant
      Corner of Magnolia Blvd. and Cartwright St. North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawing: plans, elevations, section and details.
      Owner: Mr. F.L. Winchester.
    - Rosedale Nursery., 1949.; 3.; 4 items.
      Job Number 772. Rosedale Nursery
      Ventura Blvd. Encino, CA.
    - Oefever Store Building., 1949?; 4.; 4 items.
      Job Number 775. Oefever Store Building
      Sespe St. Fillmore, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, elevations, details.
      Owner: Mr. Oscar Oefever.
  - ., 1950 (Folder 58)
    - Income Development Motel., 1950.; 1.; 1 item.
      Job Number 811. Income Development Motel Addition
      6235 Lankershiem Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawing: plan, interior elevations and section.
      Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Woodyard.
    - Bender Store Building., 1950.; 2.; 5 items.
      Job Number 845. Bender Store Building--1950
      1650-58 103rd St. Los Angeles, CA.
      Owner: D. & J. Bender.
    - M.F.G.R Building., 1950.; 3.; 2 items.
      Job Number 853. Addition to M.F.G.R Building
      15043 Califa At. Van Nuys, CA.
      Engineer's Calculations.
      Owner: Califa Creations.
    - Swenson Store Building., 1950.; 4.; 4 items.
      See also Map folder 59, item 4.
      Job Number 857. Swenson Store Building
      Ventura Blvd. Tarzana, CA.
      Owner: Mr. David Swenson.
    - Mission Park Pharmacy., 1950.; 5.; 5 items.
      Job Number 858. Mission Park Pharmacy
      11273 Laurel Canyon Blvd. Los Angeles, CA.
      Owner: Howard & Norman Siskel.
    - Ayers Store Building., 1950.; 6.; 9 items.
      Ayers Store Building
      Sherman Way, Reseda, CA.
      Owner: Mr. Don Ayers.
  - ., 1951 (Folder 59)
    - Sunland Park Art Festival., 1951.; 1.; 1 item.
      Sunland Park Art Festival
    - 1951., 2.; 4 items.
      Job Number 864. Schulman Store Building
      15808 103rd St. Los Angeles, CA.
      Owner: Mr. I. Schulman.
    - Wells Market Building., 1951.; 3.; 1 item.
      Wells Market Building
      Woodland Hills, CA.
      Original drawing: vicinity map and plot plan.
      Owner: Dr. James E. Wells.
    - Deming Storefront Remodel., 1951, no date.; 4.; 1 item.
      Job Number 936. Deming Storefront Remodel
      13235 Ventura Blvd. Studio City, CA.
      Original drawings: plan, elevation and section.
      Owner: Mr. & Mrs. N.W Deming.
    - Swenson Office., 1951.; 5.; 1 item.
      See also Map folder 58, item 4.
      Swenson Office
      Woodman Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
      Original drawing: plans, elevations and details.
    - Bender Store Building., 1951.; 6.; 4 items.
      Job Number 899. Bender Store Building--1951
      1646 1/2-48 103rd St. Los Angeles, CA.
  - ., 1952 (Folder 60)
    - Sportsmen's Swim and Cabana Club., 1952.; 1.; 9 items.
      Job Number 733. Sportsmen's Swim and Cabana Club
      Vose Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, details, sections.
      Owner: David Harlig & Ray Fine.
    - Sportsmen's Swim and Cabana Club., 1952.; 2.; 25 items.
      Job Number 952. Sportsmen's Swim and Cabana Club
      Ventura Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
      Proposal for Lodge (Motel Apartments).
      Surveyor's plan.
      Vicinity map.
    - Lombardo Store Building., 1952.; 3.; 3 items.
      Job Number 960. Lombardo Store Building
      14040 Burbank Blvd.
      Original drawings: plan, elevations, sections and details.
      Owner: Mr. Peter Lombardo.
    - Toll and Wyatt Store Building., 1952.; 4.; 4 items.
      Job Number 962. Toll and Wyatt Store Building
      5431 Reseda Blvd. Tarzana, CA.
      Owner: Toll & Wyatt.
    - Bender Store Building., 1952.; 5.; 3 items.
      Job Number 968. Bender Store Building-- 1952
      103rd St. Los Angeles, CA.
      Original drawings: plan, elevations and sections.
      Owner: S. & J. Bender.
    - The Golden Brush., 1952.; 6.; 1 item.
      The Golden Brush--store additions
      Original drawing: Plan, elevation and details.
  - ., 1953 (Folder 61)
    - Harry Plainer., 1953.; 1.; 4 items.
      Job Number 993. Harry Plainer--auto store and shop
      17544 Reseda Blvd. Reseda, CA.
      Original drawings: elevations, section, plans, details.
      Owner: Harry Plainer.
    - Golden Bull Restaurant., 1953.; 2.; 3 items.
      See also Map folder 64, item 1.
      Job Number 53-13, 53-14. Golden Bull Restaurant--addition
      12749 Ventura Blvd. Studio City, CA.
      Original drawings: elevations, section, plan.
      Owner: Glen Billingsley.
    - Roche Lincoln Mercury., 1953.; 3.; 3 items.
      Job Number 53-15. Roche Lincoln Mercury--service garage
      4436 Lankershim Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawings: elevations, sections, plans.
  - ., 1954 (Folder 62)
    - Professional Building for Rental Enterprises Inc., 1954.; 1.; 7 items.
      Job Number 54-11. Professional Building for Rental Enterprises Inc.
      Pacific Ave. Long Beach, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, sections, details.
      Owner: Rental Enterprises Inc.
    - Office Building for Simmonds Lumber Co. Inc., 1954.; 2.; 5 items.
      Job Number 54-17. Office Building for Simmonds Lumber Co. Inc.
      8150 Vineland Ave. Sun Valley, CA.
      Owner: Simmonds Lumber Co.
    - Boesch Industrial Building., 1954.; 3.; 4 items.
      Job Number 54-24. Boesch Industrial Building
      16516 Ventura Blvd. Encino, CA.
      Owner: Francis M. Boesch.
    - Pleasant View Trailer Court., 1954.; 4.; 2 items.
      Job Number 54-43. Pleasant View Trailer Court
      Original drawings: elevations, section, plans.
      Owner: Mr. Paul Murphy.
  - ., 1955 (Folder 63)
    - Winchester Restaurant., 1955.; 1.; 3 items.
      See also Map folder 57, item 2.
      Job Number 55-1. Winchester Restaurant
      Lankershim Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, elevations, section.
    - Fleetwood Machine Products Factory Building., 1955.; 2.; 6 items.
      Job Number 55-13, 54-50, 57-9. Fleetwood Machine Products Factory Building--addition
      11439 Vanowen St. North Hollywood, CA.
    - Dr. Herr Medical Offices., 1955.; 3.; 1 item.
      Job Number 55-19. Dr. Herr Medical Offices
      Original drawings: plan, interior elevations, section.
      Owner: Dr. Herr.
    - Faires Building., 1955.; 4.; 1 item.
      Job Number 55-64. Faires Building--addition
      530 Transamerica Bldg. Los Angeles, CA.
      Original drawings: plan, section, interior and exterior elevation.
  - ., 1956 (Folder 64)
    - Golden Bull Restaurant., 1956.; 1.; 2 items.
      See also Map folder 61, item 2.
      Job Number 55-43. Golden Bull Restaurant--bar addition
    - Fiske Store Building., 1956.; 2.; 2 items.
      Job Number 56-1. Fiske Store Building--alterations
      13454 Ventura Blvd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
      Original drawings: elevations, sections, plans, structural details.
      Owner: James Fiske.
    - Round Robin Restaurant., 1956.; 3.; 4 items.
      Job Number 56-38. Round Robin Restaurant--additions and alterations
      13562 Ventura Blvd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
      Original drawings: elevations, sections, plans, details.
      Owner: Di-Jor Inc.
    - Golden Bull Restaurant., 1956.; 4.; 2 items.
      Job Number 56-45. Golden Bull Restaurant--driveway and arcade roof addition
    - Bair Office Building., 1956.; 5.; 1 item.
      Job Number 56-55. Bair Office Building
      11479 Burbank Blvd. Los Angeles, CA.
      Original drawing: elevations, section and plans.
      Owner: Mr. Watt Bair.
    - Wynn Tire Shop., 1956.; 6.; 3 items.
      Job Number 56-59. Wynn Tire Shop
      6th St. Palmdale, CA.
      Structural Notes.
  - ., 1957 (Folder 65)
    - Billingsley's Steak Ranch., 1957.; 1.; 3 items.
      Job Number 57-2. Billingsley's Steak Ranch--additions
      Highway 101, CA.
      Original drawings: exterior and interior elevations, plans.
    - Palmdale Office Building., 1957.; 2.; 8 items.
      Job Number 57-19. Palmdale Office Building
      9th Street east, Palmdale, CA.
      Set of original architectural drawings.
      Drawing Revisions.
      Owner: Mrs. O. Simmons.
    - Bill Store., 1957.; 3.; 2 items.
      Job Number 57-29. Bill Store Addition
      As proposed by Joe Alkire.
      Original drawings: plan, elevation, section.
      Owner: Mr. C.M. & C. R. Bill.
    - Watson Store Building., 1957.; 4.; 3 items.
      Job Number 57-42. Watson Store Building
      14664-66 Ventura Blvd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
      Owner: Mr. & Mrs. George Watson.
  - (1 of 2)., 1958 (Folder 66)
    - Glendale Heliport., 1958.; 1.; 3 items.
      Glendale Heliport
      Glendale, CA.
      Original drawings: preliminary plans, perspective.
    - Darakjian Apartment Motel., 1958.; 2.; 17 items.
      Job Number 58-12. Darakjian Apartment Motel
      16745 Ventura Blvd. Encino, CA.
      Perspective.
      Owner: Mr. & Mrs. John Darakjian.
    - Rosedale Nursery., 1958.; 3.; 2 items.
      See also Map folder 57, item 3 and folder 67, item 2.
      Job Number 58-14. Rosedale Nursery--remodel
      5816 San Fernando Rd. Glendale, CA.
      Original drawings for lath House, store building and warehouse: plans, sections, elevations.
    - Goodman's Tire Service Sales & Service Building., 1958.; 4.; 8 items.
      Job Number 58-15. Goodman's Tire Service Sales & Service Building
      Slauson Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
  - (2 of 2)., 1958 (Folder 67)
    - Lorio Office Building., 1958.; 1.; 8 items.
      Job Number 58-37. Lorio Office Building-- alterations
      Corner of Clarendon St. and Pacific Blvd.
      Huntington Park, CA. Original drawings: plans, details, elevations.
      Owner: Mr. Vincent Lorio.
    - Rosedale Nursery--lath house., 1958.; 2.; 7 items.
      See also Map folder 57, item 3 and folder 66, item 3.
      Job Number 58-42. Rosedale Nursery--lath house
      17257 Ventura Blvd. Encino, CA.
      Original drawings for lath House and store building: plans, details, elevations.
      Proposed Rosedale Nurseries for Woodland Hills & Monrovia: perspectives.
      Owner: E. L. Lombardi.
    - Bassett Kouri Toma Office Building., 1958.; 3.; 13 items.
      Job Number 58-47. Bassett Kouri Toma Office Building
      15445 Ventura Blvd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, elevations, sections, details, perspective.
      Structural Specifications.
  - ., 1959 (Folder 68)
    - Kester Medical Building., 1959.; 1.; 1 item.
      Kester Medical Building--an income investment corporation project
      Original drawing: plans, perspective.
      Owner: Robert H. Robinson.
    - Van Nuys Quality Dairy., 1959.; 2.; 3 items.
      See also Map folder 71, item 4.
      Job Number 59-4, 59-39. Van Nuys Quality Dairy-- addition to dairy building
      13005 Sherman Way, Van Nuys, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, elevations, sections.
      Owner: Mr. F.B. Roberts.
    - Hyden Stone Office Brokerage Office, Los Angeles., 1959.; 3.; 6 items.
      See also Map folder 69, item 4.
      Job Number 59-8. Hyden Stone Office Brokerage Office, Los Angeles-- alterations
      5657 Wilshire Blvd. Los Angeles, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, sections and elevations and details.
      Owner: Hyden Stone & Co.
    - Hyden Stone Brokerage Office, Sherman Oaks., 1959.; 4.; 3 items.
      Job Number 59-17. Hyden Stone Brokerage Office, Sherman Oaks-- alterations
      14221 Ventura Blvd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
      Original drawings: plans and sections.
    - Hyden Stone Brokerage Office, Beverly Hills., 1959.; 5.; 5 items.
      Job Number 59-18. Hyden Stone Brokerage Office, Beverly Hills-- alterations
      398 S. Beverly Drive, Beverly Hills, CA.
    - Bill Heath Ford Agency., 1959.; 6.; 1 item.
      Job Number 59-27. Bill Heath Ford Agency-- remodel
      5500 Lankershim, North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, sections and detail.
      Owner: Bill Heath.
    - Cort Cox Ford., 1959, 1963.; 7.; 2 items.
      Job Number 59-28, 63-7. Cort Cox Ford--sales office and mezzanine office
      4531 Hollywood Blvd. Los Angeles, CA.
      Original drawing: plans, sections and elevation and details.
      Owner: Cort Cox Ford- Used Cars.
    - Hyden Stone Brokerage Office, Brentwood., 1959.; 8.; 9 items.
      Job Number 59-29. Hyden Stone Brokerage Office, Brentwood-- alterations
      11828 San Vicente, Brentwood, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, sections, details, elevations, air conditioning and electrical plans.
  - ., 1960 (Folder 69)
    - Chicken coupe jump for the West Hills Hunt., 1960.; 1.; 2 items.
      Chicken coupe jump for the West Hills Hunt.
      Original drawing: elevations, section, details.
      Owner: West Hills Hunt- John Blackburn, Sec.
    - Baby Doll Cocktail Lounge., 1960.; 2.; 2 items.
      Baby Doll Cocktail Lounge--addition
      7143 Laurel Canyon Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawing: plans, section and elevations.
      Copy of additional drawing.
      Owner: Bermac Inc.
    - Sun Valley Nursery., 1960.; 3.; 5 items.
      Sun Valley Nursery--porch enclosure
      17019 Ventura Blvd. Tarzana, CA.
      Original drawings and sketches: plans and elevations.
      Calculations.
    - Hyden Stone Brokerage Office, La Jolla., 1960.; 4.; 1 item.
      See also Map folder 68.
      Job Number 60-9. Hyden Stone Brokerage Office, La Jolla
      1127 Wall St. La Jolla, CA.
      Original drawing: plan, elevations and details.
    - Lade Store Front Remodel., 1960.; 5.; 1 item.
      Job Number 60-13. Lade Store Front Remodel
      6178 Sepulveda Blvd. Los Angeles, CA.
      Original drawing: plan, sections and details.
      Owner: R.M. Lade.
    - Selber Store Building Remodel., 1960.; 6.; 6 items.
      Job Number 60-25. Selber Store Building Remodel
      5723-27 Figueroa St. Highland Park, Los Angeles, CA.
      Owner: Joseph Selber.
  - ., 1961 (Folder 70)
    - Variance request for Justice Reality., 1961.; 1.; 2 items.
      Variance request for Justice Reality
      5050 Los Angeles Ave. Santa Susana, CA.
      Original drawings: plans.
      Owner: Amalia Justice & Associates.
    - Buckley Medical Building Remodel., 1961.; 2.; 4 items.
      Job Number 61-4. Buckley Medical Building Remodel
      10117 Riverside Drive, North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, elevations, sections, electrical and mechanical plan.
      Owner: Dr. C. E. Buckley.
    - Palmer Mann--industrial building., 1961.; 3.; 10 items.
      Job Number 61-38. Palmer Mann--industrial building (J. Russel Construction Co.)
      Long Beach, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, details, elevations, sections.
      Owner: Palmer-Pann Inc.
  - ., 1962 (Folder 71)
    - Dental Building Locker Rooms and Lounge., 1962.; 1.; 1 item.
      Dental Building Locker Rooms and Lounge
      Original drawing: section, plan and detail.
    - Treasure Island Thieves Market Swap Meet., 1962.; 2.; 6 items.
      Treasure Island Thieves Market Swap Meet
      15826 Magnolia Blvd. Encino, CA and 4777 N. Las Virgenes Rd. Calabasas, CA.
      Original drawings: sections, elevations and plans.
      Owner: Stanley Dorn.
    - Carphin., 1962.; 3.; 2 items.
      Job Number 62-2. Carphin--shop units
      Owner: Mr. Wm. M. Carphin.
    - Van Nuys Quality Dairy., 1962.; 4.; 3 items.
      See also Map folder 68, item 2.
      Job Number 62-5. Van Nuys Quality Dairy-- Additions
      General notes and specifications.
    - McNally Azar Realtors., 1962.; 5.; 1 item.
      Job Number 62-17. McNally Azar Realtors-- Office Layout
      Original drawing: plan, exterior and interior elevations, screen detail.
      Owner: McNally Azar realtors.
  - ., 1963 (Folder 72)
    - Janda Store Building., 1963.; 1.; 9 items.
      Job Number 63-1. Janda Store Building
      Van Nuys Blvd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
      Original drawing: plans, sections, elevations and details and heating and air-conditioning layout.
      Owner: Joseph W. Janda.
    - Curry Automotive Garage., 1963.; 2.; 4 items.
      Job Number 63-8. Curry Automotive Garage
      8011 Sepulveda Blvd. Van Nuys, CA.
      Original drawing: plans, sections, elevations and details.
      Owner: Roger Curry.
    - Hughs Real Estate Office., 1963.; 3.; 1 item.
      Job Number 63-20. Hughs Real Estate Office
      Ventura Blvd. at Lewis Rd. Agoura, CA.
      Original drawing: plans, sections and elevations.
      Owner: Elizabeth Hughs.
    - Ned King Garage., 1963.; 4.; 1 item.
      Job Number 63-23. Ned King Garage
      11666 Ventura Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawing: plans and elevations.
      Owner: Ned King.
    - Norman Larson Company., 1963.; 5.; 1 item.
      Job Number 63-26. Norman Larson Company--stairway
      5910 Avion Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
      Original drawing: details and elevations.
    - Rancho Del Valle., 1963.; 6.; 10 items.
      Job Number 63-30. Rancho Del Valle--swimming pool enclosure
      6530 Minnetka Ave. Woodland Hills, CA.
      Original drawing: plans, sections, details and elevations.
      Color Perspectives.
      Engineer's notes.
      Timber Company schedule.
  - ., 1964 (Folder 73)
    - Konopla Rental building., 1964.; 1.; 1 item.
      Konopla Rental building
      5338 Vineland, North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawing: plan.
    - Baldwin Piano Company., 1964.; 2.; 2 items.
      Job Number 64-3. Baldwin Piano Company--store front remodeling
      3273 Wilshire Blvd. Los Angeles, CA.
      Original drawing and copy: plan, elevation and section.
      Owner: Ralph Louis, manager.
    - Mary's Coffee Shop., 1964.; 3.; 1 item.
      Job Number 64-9. Mary's Coffee Shop
      13511 Muscatine St. Arleta, CA.
      Owner: Mr. & Mrs. George Gear.
  - ., 1965 (Folder 74)
    - C. & C. Dairy Plant., 1965?; 1.; 1 item.
      C. & C. Dairy Plant
      Los Angeles Ave. Ventura County, CA.
      Original drawing: plans.
      Owner: Harold Cliff.
    - Abbott Studio and Office., 1965?; 2.; 1 item.
      Abbott Studio and Office
      513 1/2 E. Broadway, Glendale, CA.
      Original drawing: plan, elevation and section.
    - Shasta Trailers Office., 1965.; 3.; 3 items.
      Job Number 65-16. Shasta Trailers Office Additions
      9401 Tampa Ave. Northridge, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, elevations and details.
      Owner: Robert Gray.
    - Lou Ehler Cadillac., 1965.; 4.; 5 items.
      Job Number 65-17. Lou Ehler Cadillac--remodel
      5151 Wilshire Blvd. Los Angeles, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, interior elevations and perspective.
      Owner: Lou Ehler.
  - ., 1966 (Folder 75)
    - Wallichs Music Center., 1966.; 1.; 1 item.
      Wallichs Music Center-- alterations
      1526 Ivar, Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawing: elevation and plan.
    - Canoga Farms., 1966.; 2.; 6 items.
      Job Number 66-18. Canoga Farms--wine sales building
      17555 Ventura Blvd. Encino, CA.
      Original drawings and copies: plans, interior elevations and details.
      Owner: R.S. Norswing (Eleanor Fozzard, contact person).
  - ., 1967 (Folder 76)
    - Beverly Hills Ford., 1967.; 1.; 5 items.
      Job Number 67-10. Beverly Hills Ford--remodel (William Philip Wachsman, I.D.S.A).
      KFWB Radio, 6419 Hollywood Blvd. Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawings and copies: "as is" plans.
    - Beverly Hills Ford., 1967.; 2.; 2 items.
      Job Number 67-16. Beverly Hills Ford--remodel (William Philip Wachsman, I.D.S.A).
      Beverly Hills, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, sections, interior elevations.
    - Glore Forgen Staats Stocks & Bonds., 1967.; 3.; 1 item.
      Job Number 67-22. Glore Forgen Staats Stocks & Bonds--office remodel
      50 Fashion Square, Sherman Oaks, CA.
      Original drawing: plans, interior elevations and sections.
      Owner: Robert Gale.
    - Neuman Office Building., 1967.; 4.; 1 item.
      Job Number 67-23. Neuman Office Building--addition
      3412 Victory Blvd. Burbank, CA.
      Owner: Mrs. B. Neuman.
  - ., 1968-1969 (Folder 77)
    - Bull Pen Restaurant., 1968.; 1.; 1 item.
      See also Map folder 56, item 5.
      Bull Pen Restaurant--remodel
      Original Drawing: plan.
    - Lipner & Bloom Commercial Building., 1968.; 2.; 2 items.
      Job Number 68-3. Lipner & Bloom Commercial Building
      11105 Burbank Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
      Original Drawings: elevations, plans and sections.
      Owner: E.R. Lipner & Dr. S.M. Bloom.
    - Bull Pen Jr. Restaurant., 1969.; 3.; 1 item.
      Job Number 69-33. Bull Pen Jr. Restaurant--new mansard parapet
      10351 San Fernando Rd.
      Original Drawing: elevation, detail and plan.
- Series 4: Clubs., 1963
  Civic institutions.
  - Sherman Oaks Woman's Clubhouse (1 of 2)., 1963.; 22 items. (Folder 78)
    Job Number 63-14. Sherman Oaks Woman's Clubhouse
    4808 Kester Ave. Sherman Oaks, CA.
    Original drawings: plans, section, elevations and details.
    Original and two copies of perspectives.
    Carpentry Shop drawings.
    Owner: Sherman Oaks Woman's Club.
  - Sherman Oaks Woman's Clubhouse (2 of 2)., 1963.; 10 items. (Folder 79)
    Copy of drawings: plans, section, elevations and details.
- Series 5: Residential projects., 1939-1970
  Series arranged in the following subseries:
  A. Apartments, 1945-1970 (30 map folders).
  B. Private homes, 1939-1970 (73 map folders).
  C. Additions and renovations, 1939-1968 (30 map folders).
  D. Model and tract homes, 1947-1964 (30 folders).
  - Subseries A: Apartments., 1945-1970.; 30 map folders.
    Designs range from three-unit buildings to 70-unit residential complexes.
    - Apartments--miscellaneous (1 of 2)., no date.; ca. 15 items. (Folder 80)
      Apartments--sketches
      Untitled sketches of plans and sections.
      Possibly related to the Spoon Apartments, 1968 (folder 107).
    - Apartments--miscellaneous (2 of 2)., no date.; ca. 20 items. (Folder 81)
      Apartments--Thousand Oaks
      Untitled plans, sections and perspectives.
      Owner: McInnis Construction Company.
    - ., 1945-1946 (Folder 82)
      - Stanley Apartments., 1945?; 1.; 1 item.
        Stanley Apartments
        Venice, CA. 4 units.
        Original drawing: plan and elevation.
        Owner: Albert Stanley.
      - Nan-Rich Apartments., 1945.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 469. Nan-Rich Apartments
        Pass Ave. Burbank, CA.
        17 units?
        Original drawings: plans, sections, details and plot plan.
        Owner: Mr. B. H. Vlock.
      - Murphy Apartment and Store Building., 1946.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 527. Murphy Apartment and Store Building
        Whitsett Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
    - (1 of 3)., 1947 (Folder 83)
      - Bourgeau Apartments., 1947.; 25 items.
        Job Number 537. Bourgeau Apartments
        4761- 4775 1/2 Sepulveda Blvd. Los Angeles CA.
        16 Units and 36 units.
        Owner: Leon Bourgeau.
    - (2 of 3)., 1947 (Folder 84)
      - Beck Apartments., 1947.; 1.; 6 items.
        See also Map folders 85 and 86.
        Job Number 604. Beck Apartments Van Nuys
        Van Owen St. Van Nuys, CA.
        2 units.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. D. E. Beck.